(Bernadette:)-Great.
-Really?
(Penny:)You think I'm putting
this body through three kids?
(Sheldon:)Okay, let's do this.
(Howard:)Good luck.
(Amy:)You...
Aren't you gonna come with me?
(Howard:)While you confront your mother
about her sex life?
(Howard:)I'd rather go back to that bar
in ass-less chaps.
(Sheldon:)Mother?
Mother?
(Sheldon:)Mother.
Shelly!
I'm so glad you're here!
(Sheldon:)I saw you having naked sex.
(Mrs Cooper:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)Earlier, I came here to surprise you.
(Sheldon:)I looked in the window
and I saw you with a man.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, Shelly, I'm so sorry.
Come in.
(Bernadette:)Um...
(Mrs Cooper:)Maybe we should sit down
and talk about this.
(Sheldon:)Can you recommend a surface
you haven't had coitus on?